<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>My Fish Log (flog)</title>
<link>http://home.earthlink.net/~joseph-ja/fish_log.xml</link>
<description>This is my sort of fish log of flog. Not quite a blog, but it is the start of some type of log.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<managingEditor>me@avoidingspam.com</managingEditor>
<webMaster>me@avoidingspam.com</webMaster>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 04:09:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<generator>godura</generator>

<item>
<title>Christmas updates, December 2016.</title>
<description>Midnight was a black moor now deceased.  Belle was an orange,white and slightly red female Oranda that I had to give away on 1/5/2013.  Pepper was a malke calico telescope with breeding tuberculosis.  Pepper passed away early in 2016. Paprika is new calico telescope obtained on 11 / 2015.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12d1464748}</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>More fish updates, June 2012.</title>
<description>I have separated the 2 sick fish.  I have 2 male guppies and 2 female guppies and neither is breeding.  My white clouds are not breeding either.  My plants however are growing.  My Amazon swords have both sent out 2 runners that are developing into new plants.  I guess I need to start selling plants again at the local aquarium society.  I wish I knew what to do to make all my fish start doing better.  Maybe I need swords in all my tanks?  Problem with swords is that they get huge.  </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12d1234a4ff}</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 1 Ju1 2012 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Goldfish updates.</title>
<description>Turns out Tangerine is a girl and Shadow is a boy.  So they laid eggs, in December, and I rescued a few. They did this again in March and April.  I have saved a few.  Out of the first batch I raised one.  Out of the second I raised 2 and out of the third, I raised 3.  The oldest of the fry is now upside down.  Also one of the second batch of fry is swimming sideways.  Not looking good for either of them.   </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12d1234a4ff}</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 1 Ju1 2012 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Got new Goldfish, October 2011.</title>
<description>Got new goldfish.  One black moor about 2", one calico telescope about 1.5", and one oranda about 1.5". Just put them in the 20 and moved the male guppies out for now.  Will quarantine them for a week and then move them to the 40 gallon tank. </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12d1234a4ff}</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 1 Ju1 2012 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Got new Goldfish, July 2011.</title>
<description>Got new goldfish.  One black moor about 1.5" and one orange telescope about 2.5".  They have been added into the 40 gallon tank.  Goldfish are supposed to be good luck.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12d1234a4ff}</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 July 2011 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>More guppy babies, July 2011.</title>
<description>My guppies are at 3 brood.  I have separated two females into a 2.5 gallon tank.  The fish are going to be breed with a nice blue male. I will be separating 2 more females into another 2.5 gallon tank to breed with a red male.  Goal is to breed blue males and red males with blue females and red females, but will start with blond bodied females.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-bbad1234a4ff}</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 17 July 2011 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>New catfish, July 2011.</title>
<description>Got 4 new bushy nosed plecos.  They are all albinos and about 2-2.5" long.  Added to my 20 gallon tank.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-bbad1abfa4ff}</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 8 July 2011 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>White Cloud Minnow Juveniles, November 2009.</title>
<description>Six of the juveniles were moved to the main tank at the beginning of November.  First one was added and then when it was noted that he was swimming along fine with the adults White Cloud Minnows, Cherry Barbs, and Serpae Tetras 6 more were added to the adult tank.  Eight of the juveniles were sold to someone else who keeps Zebra Danio's.  The remaining fish were distributed among the 40, the 20 and then 10.  The juveniles in the 40 have disappeared, probably into the mouths of the clown barbs.  The rest seem to be doing ok.     </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12df059a4ff}</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>White Cloud Minnow More About Fry, October 2009.</title>
<description>It was probably the last week of September when I noticed a small fry.  Most of the fry were about 1/2 inch but this one was much smaller.  As a result of his small size I separated him from the rest.  By 10/4 it had been a week since I separated him from the rest.  I am not sure if he is a runt or not.  I will watch him carefully.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12df059a110}</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 5 Jun 2009 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>White Cloud Minnow Fry, September 2009.</title>
<description>9/1 Some fry were darting.  By 9/6 I had counted at least a dozen.  On 9/8 I tried feeding them frozen baby brine shrimp.  On 9/13 I was feeding them baby brine shrimp twice a day.  On 9/16 I transferred them into a large critter keeper.  On 9/18 I did the first 50% water change.  Prior to this the water changes done were minor and very carefully done as to make sure that fry were not siphoned off.  </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12df059a1f9}</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 5 Jun 2009 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>White Cloud Minnow Eggs.</title>
<description>On August 29, 2009 I put a male and female white cloud together.  On August 30, 2009 they laid eggs.  On August 31, 2009 a large percent got fuzzy.  Some hatched in about 24 to 36 hours.  </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12df059a1e8}</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 5 Jun 2009 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Saturday April 7, new rosy barb eggs were laid.</title>
<description>I saw my rosy barbs doing what fish do and so I tried to get some eggs out of the floating plants.  Well 2 days later it looks like it worked.  There are a few baby rosy barb wigglers. </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{ceff318d-d9d3-a28-2de4-b12df059a1e7}</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2008 04:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>New fish, one month after all the fish died. </title>
<description>So on Saturday the 24th I got some new fish.  I got 3 guppies, 1 powder blue gourami, 6 rosy barbs, and 6 cory cats.  The cory cats went into my 20 gallon tank, after I moved 2 bushy nosed plecos out of the tank.  Now my 20 gallon has 3 platies, 6 cories, and 2 bush nosed plecos.  The rosy barbs went into my 40 gallon, with my firemouth and the 2 busy nosed plecos I moved out of my 20 gallon.  The guppies went into my 6 gallon where they died in a few hours, even though there was no ammonia, nitrates, or nitrites showing up in my test kits.  The gourami went into a small container where it stayed until today the 24th.  Today the gourami went into my 10 gallon tank and it seems to be doing fine.  The cories are doing okay, but the barbs, seem to have with stuff on their fins.  I also got 5 new guppies today from a different store.  So far so good, but I need to keep an eye on my barbs, and the new guppies.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{316c9ce3-bb30-3ae9-37a7-e31e53e1cbcc}</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2007 01:22:06 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>All my rosy barbs died :-(</title>
<description>So I went on vacation and before vacation all my rosy barbs looked peaked, I think from overfeeding.  When I got back it was a matter of days and they had all died.  The youngest were about 5 months old and the oldest were over a year old or more.  It was a sad week because of this.  Maybe I'll get more after I clean up the tank.  </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{d5833645-3f02-a2f5-e1e3-83c7bf699cc}</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2007 19:58:32 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Babies showing more colors</title>
<description>While the fish have not started to show imuch color in their body, the fins are beginning to color up rather nicely.  They are showing black and red in the fins.  So far none of the babies have started to show the longfins, but they are only a few months old.  I'd expect by 6 month old they would be showing beautiful colors like their parents.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{b760fa13-ad00-c86e-fd09-b70ad68c267}</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 18:21:40 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rosy Barb fry update!</title>
<description>Well the fry are no longer fry, but juveniles.  On September 9th, 2006, the first set of fry are now 76 days old.  The juveniles are about 1-1/2 to 2 inches long.  Some of the juveniles are beginning to show black color in their dorsals, but so far no color in their bodies other than the black spot at the base of the tails and the silver color that most rosy barbs display.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{34210af-a7cb-e6e6-b719-270e2c931149}</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2007 00:00:57 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Over a month after my Rosy Barbs laid eggs!</title>
<description>It has been about 5 weeks, since my rosy barbs have laid eggs and the fry have hatch.   I have moved the 5 week old Rosy Barbs to my 20 gallon tank with some platies and suckermouth catfish.  So far they seem to be doing very well.  I am feeding them twice a day a mix of frozen foods that includes brine shrimp, bloodworms, and some veggie mix.  They love the food and some are now 1 inch long.  There are around 11 fish in this batch.  There is a second batch of 6 fish that is a week younger or so younger.  Once they start showing color and I can sex them I'll start looking into a breeding program for these fish.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{87aa21de-ae1-822b-8fbd-b0c4d769809}</guid>
<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2007 18:18:43 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Two weeks since the first eggs were laid!</title>
<description>Rosy Barb eggs seem to hatch in about two or three days.  It has been 2 weeks since the first batch of eggs were laid.  There are more than 8 fry from the first batch.  The first batch of fry are all about the size of guppy fry and seem to be doing fine.  Feeding baby brine shrimp twice a day seems to be helping them grow quick.  I use a hard tube, that has the same diameter of airline tubing to doign water changes.  The hard tube is connected to airline tubing.  Using this type of setup I can do water changes and clean the bottom of the tank as well.  Not having any gravel or anything on the bottom of the tank has helped to see how much stuff is in the tank.  This helps keep it clean.  </description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{51c849ae-cf26-9c74-2128-64b83926321}</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:47:26 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Second batch of fry!</title>
<description>On Sunday July 1, 2007 I saw my Rosy Barbs going at it again and breeding.  I already had a few babies in my 3 gallon eclipse, but I figured I could try to raise a few more.  I again took some plants and shook them out into the 3 gallon tank.  The original batch are in the same container.  The first batch is doing fine.</description>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{56c6fd6-f727-3114-1c7b-e0ab50206eb5}</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:41:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>New Baby Rosy Barbs!</title>
<description>On Saturday June 30th I moved the Rosy Barb babies from the 1 gallon aquarium into the 3 gallon eclipse.  I cleaned out the eclipse first, and then used water from the main 40 gallon tank.  The babies are really small. Because I was not sure what to feed them, I went to the pet store.  The owner of the store is really knowledgable and he told me to use frozen baby brine shrimp.  He said to feed 6 times a day.  Since I am not home enough to feed them that often, I feed them twice a day.  I feed the fry once in the morning and once in the evening.  I turn on the light for about 30 minutes.  I have been running an airstone during the days and turning it off at night so they can sleep.  I have started doing 20% water changes every evening.</description>
<category>Rosy Barbs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{5c6abc9e-9721-c854-e19c-baa606e304c}</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Rosy barbs laid eggs and had Caviar.</title>
<description>On Sunday June 24, 2007, my Rosy Barbs laid eggs.  Because I have lots of floating plants it took them a while to eat them.  As a result of them taking so long and breeding for several hours, I was able to rescue about 20 eggs.  I had read somewhere that if the eggs turn white then they are not fertilized and if they stay clear then they are fertilized.  In 24 hours most of the eggs have turned white, except for about 3 to 5.  On Monday I moved the container with the eggs into my 3 gallon eclipse and turned the heater on.  The temperature is about 79 degrees.  The eggs are about 1 millimeter, and the hatchlings are about 2 millimeters and clear.  Lets see if I can raise one or two.    </description>
<category>Rosy Barbs</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">{200c1c4-9642-c47f-9a04-c97a8a2511b0}</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>March, 2007 I lost a firemouth, but my tanks are clearing up!</title>
<description>March 11, 2007 I lost one of my firemouths.  I had the fish for about 3 years or more.  The two firemouths got into fighting and this one lost.  On a more pleasant note, both my 40 gallon and my 20 gallon tanks have cleared up.  The water in the tanks is almost completely clear and the green is gone.  I attribute this to the addition of some fast growing floating plants.  I'll be increasing the light cycle again over the next month or two.  
	</description>
	<category>Firemouth</category>
	<guid isPermaLink="false">{28ac5484-682b-94ba-93f2-3bbf93791182}</guid>
	<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>
	<item>
	<title>February, 2007 I lost a platy, but my 40 is clearing up!</title>
	<description>One of my platies (variatus) died in my 20 gallon.  The tank is pretty green, but not as green as it used to be.  I can see a little deeper into the tank.  My 40 gallon tank has cleared up a bit.  In tthe 40 gallon tank, I havereduced the light by about an hour.  I am not using CO2 in my 40 gallon, and the plants get a little torn up by the firemouths and rosy barbs.  I guess the plants don"t need all that much light.  My guess is that the room gets a lot of light during the day, so I do not need to leave teh tank light on as long.  
		</description>
		<category>Platies</category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">{a4998ef8-bb7f-9189-4f26-e0cc7ad15250}</guid>
		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:02:17 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>January, 2007 I lost a rosy barb.</title>
		<description>One of my rosy barbs died in my 40 gallon.  The tank is a little green, but not as green as my 20 gallon long.  Is it something in the water or just to much light?
			</description>
			<category>Rosy Barbs</category>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">{488cf9d-2609-8bf6-8ea3-6e3621245047}</guid>
			<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:02:08 GMT</pubDate>
			</item>
			<item>
			<title>December, 2006 All of my new female bettas are gone!</title>
			<description>I'm really kind of sad, because I lost all of my females.  
				</description>
				<category>Bettas</category>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">{fcfa7ef2-bf2a-7a4e-8ddb-43f97af9bb03}</guid>
				<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
				</item>
				<item>
				<title>December 10, 2006 One of my new females died!</title>
				<description>I'm really kind of sad, because I lost one of my female bettas.  They seemed to be doing so well.  Then over the past few days she started to have a fungus on her head.  I tried separating her and then she died.  I think I have overcrowded the little fish.  I had 3 female bettas in a 3 gallon eclipse.  They seemed to be doing okay. 
					</description>
					<category>Bettas</category>
					<guid isPermaLink="false">{14657013-35f5-e7b5-35e5-5c403985ea49}</guid>
					<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:01:57 GMT</pubDate>
					</item>
					<item>
					<title>October 28, 2006 Got 3 female Copper Blue-Green Bettas</title>
					<description>I went to the California Betta Society meeting and got 3 female bettas.  I think the seller said they were copper and blue mix, but the look more blue-green to me.  
						</description>
						<category>Bettas</category>
						<guid isPermaLink="false">{63135d61-4832-c286-3e91-6fe7c7c0341b}</guid>
						<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:01:53 GMT</pubDate>
						</item>
						<item>
						<title>October 14, 2006 Rosy barbs Lay Eggs!</title>
						<description>This morning, at about 10am, my rosy barbs (Puntius conchonius) started laying eggs.
							Unlike cichlids, the fish just kind of shot them out all over the place.  
								It looked like about 30 or so eggs were dispelled.  
									At first I was not sure what was going on, but when 
										I approached the aquarium, I noticed that they were eggs.
											The eggs  were roundi, smaller than a convict cichlid (Archocentrus nigrofasciatus) eggs, 
												but islightly larger than betta eggs.  
													I have no idea if they were fertilized or not, but it has inspired me to attempt to setup
														some sort of breeding aquarium.  I wonder if I can selectively breed an all black rosy barb?
															</description>
															<category>Rosy Barbs</category>
															<guid isPermaLink="false">{d7e3cea6-a881-286c-cd5-b100f70fb516}</guid>
															<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:01:38 GMT</pubDate>
															</item>
															<item>
															<title>September 2006 New 40 Gallon Tank</title>
															<description>On September 23, 2006 I got a new 40 gallon acrylic aquarium.
																I'm replacing my 50 gallon with the 40 gallon, because the 50 gallon has a 
																	built in wet dry filter that I find difficult to clean.
																		I'm going to move the fish from my 20 gallon aquarium to my 40 gallon to give them
																			more space.
																				</description>
																				<category>General</category>
																				<guid isPermaLink="false">{40f73fbf-82a1-7745-6daa-d25b6a9fb210}</guid>
																				<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:01:33 GMT</pubDate>
																				</item>
																				<item>
																				<title>September 2006 Tank Setups</title>
																				<description>It's now September 2006.
																					I have the following tank setups: a 3 gallon eclipse tank with some small feeder guppies; 
																						a 10 gallon Odyssea aquarium with some nicer guppies and some java ferns;  
																							a 20 gallon TruVu with 2 firemouths, 12 rosy barbs, 3 clown plecos, and 2 Ancistrus ( it's way overstocked );
																								and a 50 gallon S&amp;S aquarium with 3 convicts.
																									</description>
																									<category>General</category>
																									<guid isPermaLink="false">{973f9ecb-cdb-29c6-8c43-53121061f9fb}</guid>
																									<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:01:27 GMT</pubDate>
																									</item>
																									<item>
																									<title>Rosy Barbs</title>
																									<description>In June I bought 6 rosy barbs, and at the beginning of July 2006 I got 6 more.
																										I added these fish into my 20 gallon tank. So far all are doing well. 
																											They are in my 20 gallon tank with a couple of firemouth cichlids.
																												</description>
																												<category>Rosy Barbs</category>
																												<guid isPermaLink="false">{4be978df-d595-46e7-c2ac-451b36a1ef0f}</guid>
																												<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:00:03 GMT</pubDate>
																												</item>
																												<item>
																												<title>20 Gallon Acrylic</title>
																												<description>In early 2006 I got rid of my 20 gallon glass aquarium and traded it for an acrylic aquarium.
																													</description>
																													<category>General</category>
																													<guid isPermaLink="false">{c2e9f977-2d0f-8a8-d405-cbcfa4d21c19}</guid>
																													<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:59:02 GMT</pubDate>
																													</item>
																													<item>
																													<title>Firemouth Lifespan</title>
																													<description>As of 2006 one firemouth I have had since 2001, so it is about 5 years old. 
																														One died and I replaced it with a new firemouth in about 2004. 
																															My original convicts had babies after I got rid of the Jack Dempsey. 
																																Their babies had babies. I still have some of the second generation and 3rd generation convicts.</description>
																																<category>Firemouth</category>
																																<guid isPermaLink="false">{6e2982d2-906e-ad60-ecf-ca6b87f3c096}</guid>
																																<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:00:13 GMT</pubDate>
																																</item>
																																<item>
																																<title>The One Eyed Convict</title>
																																<description>In early 2006 I also had a convict get into a serious fight.  
																																	I now call him Sigh.  In this fight he lost and eye and got a really bad case of fungus.  
																																		I seperated him into a 3 gallon aquarium and now he is doing better.  
																																			He still has one eye, and I really do not think it would grow back, so I have named him Sigh, as in cyclops.  
																																				Why Sigh?  Because we live in an age when names are spelled anyway you fell like spelling them.  
																																					So this is how I fell like spelling his name.  
																																						I am not sure of how old Sigh is, but I believe I got his parents in 2001 and then sold them in 2003.  
																																							I believe he was born in 2003, so now he is about 3 years old in 2006.</description>
																																							<category>General</category>
																																							<guid isPermaLink="false">{562cbf6b-d267-e669-e181-89ccc4144d50}</guid>
																																							<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:58:27 GMT</pubDate>
																																							</item>
																																							<item>
																																							<title>Jack Dempsey is Sold!</title>
																																							<description>In early 2004 I sold my Jack Dempsey.  He was just to big for the fish and
																																								beating up on the other fish.  I think it was about 7 or 8 inches from head to tail.
																																									I think he got a good new home.  I sold him on craigslist.org.
																																										</description>
																																										<category>General</category>
																																										<guid isPermaLink="false">{83be9f94-38b2-34ca-e42d-d1c355902133}</guid>
																																										<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 04:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
																																										</item>
																																										<item>
																																										<title>50 Gallon S&amp;S Aquarium Setup</title>
																																										<description>I've replaced my 12 gallon eclipse with a 50 gallon S&amp;S aquarium.
																																											The 50 gallon aquarium has an internal wet-dry filter.
																																												I've discovered that I do not like this filter, as it sucks in small fish like guppies.
																																													Also when it clogs the water does not go into the filter, it stays in the tank and then overflows into the filter.
																																														I have 1 jack Dempsey in the tank 2 Convicts ( a male and female ) and 2 Firemouths and 1 Ancistrus catfish.
																																															</description>
																																															<category>General</category>
																																															<guid isPermaLink="false">{f6f0de6-1-8b1e-2107-6b5dbe635f6}</guid>
																																															<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:58:09 GMT</pubDate>
																																															</item>
																																															<item>
																																															<title>12 Gallon Eclipse Gone</title>
																																															<description>By about 2003, my 12 gallon eclipse is now gone.  
																																																I sold it on craigslist.org.  I've since replaced it with a larger tank.</description>
																																																<category>General</category>
																																																<guid isPermaLink="false">{dfabcc11-26b3-4f1d-1426-7b951ce7ef5f}</guid>
																																																<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:58:03 GMT</pubDate>
																																																</item>
																																																<item>
																																																<title>6 gallon tank Troubles</title>
																																																<description>By 2003, I was not having huge success with my 6 gallon aquarium.  
																																																	It's probably my fault, but it's gone now.</description>
																																																	<category>General</category>
																																																	<guid isPermaLink="false">{cf214d34-5aa4-2ce9-5ca3-880b263580cf}</guid>
																																																	<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:57:53 GMT</pubDate>
																																																	</item>
																																																	<item>
																																																	<title>6 Gallon Eclipse Setup</title>
																																																	<description>About 2001 I setup a 6 gallon eclipse tank.</description>
																																																	<category>General</category>
																																																	<guid isPermaLink="false">{96b76c39-bc03-6b10-23ce-5dad4e1e33}</guid>
																																																	<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:59:41 GMT</pubDate>
																																																	</item>
																																																	<item>
																																																	<title>20 Gallon Glass Tank Setup</title>
																																																	<description>Intially setup 20 gallon glass aquarium.  
																																																		This was around early 2000, probably about March. </description>
																																																		<category>General</category>
																																																		<guid isPermaLink="false">{43ab6fe-c301-b206-ddd8-9fbba1dc8bae}</guid>
																																																		<pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2007 03:59:36 GMT</pubDate>
																																																		</item>
																																																		</channel>
																																																		</rss>

