<?xml version="1.0"?>
<tropical_fish>

   <fish_data>
        <name>Bristol Nosed Cats</name>
        <comment>
       &#160;&#160;&#160;In my years of tropical fish keeping, I
have kept many different fish. One of my favorite species to keep is
the Bristol Nosed Cats. The species of bristol cats that I have kept
usually grew to be around 4 inches in size and the males are the ones with the
bristols while the females did not have bristols. This is my attempt at
documenting some of the conditions that were present in my aquarium
while breeding these little cats.
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;The water quality was tested with Dr.
Wellfish test kits. The ammonia was approximately 0ppm, the nitrate was
approximately 0ppm, and the pH was at about 7.6 possibly higher and
sometimes lower as low as 6.0. These cats can with stand various types
of water quality but mine seemed to have done best when the pH was
around 7.6. I am not sure what the hardness of the water was though.
The temperature was usually around 72 degrees, though the tank was not
heated. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;The main tank was a 20 gallon long, although
I have also breed them in a 15 gallon. All the tanks have always had
gravel bottoms and usually some floating plants as well as some rooted
plants like Anubis. The Anubis seemed to do well under the same
conditions as the cats. I only used 1 light bulb in the tank. I usually
gave them rock shelters too. I have also found that a piece of bog wood
helps but is not necessary for breeding. The cats use the bog wood for
gnawing on and do like to hide on or under it. Usually the cats breed
on the bottom side of a rock shelter. My rock shelters were basically a
flat rock that was laid on either one or two round rocks to form a cave
that gave them a hiding place. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;I feed the cats shrimp pellets. This
was a high protein diet, and seemed to do well for the adults. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;The number of other fish in the tanks varied
from time to time. Often I kept anywhere from 2 females cats and one
male to three males and 2 females and several babies and juveniles. At
one point there were 80+ babies that I was able to raise to about 1.5
inches and then sell them. It seemed more important to keep the water
quality well than the number of fish. Good water quality meant no
ammonia or nitrates/nitrites. I also kept guppies in these tanks.
However they never bred when guppies were in the tank, or if they did
the guppies may have gotten to the babies. I tried keeping them with
small Central American cichlids once, but the cichlids are too
aggressive and stressed the cats. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;The changing of water usually seemed
to be the trigger to them spawning. This must have been because of the
sudden change in the water conditions from a lower pH to a higher pH.
The spawning usually occurred after water change or after moving fish
from one tank to another tank of better water conditions. More often
than not when they breed once they mate several times, and sometimes
there are multiple females involved. If they are kept well fed they
will not harm the young. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;I am not sure why they reproduced so
much, they just did. I never tried to make them reproduce, I just hoped
and they did. Good water conditions are a must for fish to mate so I
guess I must have been doing something right. I'd recommend not keeping
them with any other bottom feeders or any large fish. Best bet would be
livebearers, schooling fish or any other middle or top level small none
aggressive fish. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Bristol Nosed Cats (Ancistrus T or D?)
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;The cats I kept were sexually dimorphic i.e. they could be
easily sexed. The males had the bristols.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They were somewhat aggressive towards other males, but I
never had them kill each other, at least that I know of.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They could withstand just about any pH, but I think the
water was acidic. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They were egg layers in which the male catfish usually
protected the young till they left the nest. Sometimes they eat the
eggs.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They may eat anything they can catch and fit in their
mouth, I fed mine shrimp pellets. They were excellent algae eaters.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They grew to about 3.5 to 4.5 inches.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;I have kept one in a 6 gallon tank, or a trio in a 15
gallon tank, or 4 to 5 in a 20 gallon tank.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
        </comment>
   </fish_data>

   <fish_data>
        <name>Cichlids</name>
        <comment>
&#160;&#160;&#160;I have keep many different types of
cichlids. I like keeping these fish too. I have kept Oscars, Convicts,
Firemouths, Port Acaras, Blue Acaras, some small African cichlids that
I am not sure what they were, as well as the Texas cichlid, Angel fish,
Blue Rams, a Jack Dempsey and possibly several others that I cannot
remember. Most of
the cichlids I have kept have been from South or Central America.&#160;
Although my favorite cichlid is the Oscar,&#160; I usually try to keep
Convicts instead as they can live in a smaller tank space. An Oscar will grow to
about a foot while my Convicts only grow to about 4 to 5 inches or so.
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;When I had my Oscars I raised these fish
from about 1.5 inches to about 10 inches in about 2 years. If I were to
do it again I'd have gotten a 75 to 90 gallon tank for the pair that I
had. I was able to sex them at about 1 year. I was not absolutely sure
which was which, but was pretty sure by their behavior that they were a
pair. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160; While not all cichlids form 'permanant life
pair bonds', they do exhibit pairing behavior.&#160; Usually two
cichlids of will swim very close to each other.&#160; Often thie rfins
will tough and they will pass very close to each other.&#160; They also
did head to tail touching. Their pectoral fins would touch, as would they touch tails.
Often the tail fin of one would touch the body of the other. It is always pretty interesting to
watch. They acted almost civil to each other at times because they seemed to like
'touching' each other. They did do some jaw locking as is seen in some
other cichlids, but it was more like kissing of sorts. It was not until
I actually saw them laying their eggs that I realized that I was right
about which was the male and which was the female. They would lay their
eggs on the bottom side of a flower pot that was out in the open.
Although the eggs hatched I was never able to raise the young. I had
the same problem with my Blue Rams when they laid their eggs. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160; Convicts seemed to like to breed in an open space. They
usually made good parents if they did not eat their young. I have also kept and breed Firemouths.
Their behavior was similar to that of the Oscars and Convicts. The
main differences that I observed was the Firemouths seamed to prefer to
lay their eggs in a cave, typically on the underside of a flat piece of
slate rock or on the inside of a flower pot. The second major
difference is that they were not as friendly to each other as the
Oscars seemed to be. My Convicts seemed to form pair bonds and be somewhat
friendly to each other. The Convicts were very aggressive.
At one point I had a two female Convicts that exhibited the same
behavior as a male/female pair. I referred to them as my lesbian
convicts ;-).&#160; I have also heard of stories of angel fish and
discus also dispaying lesbian behavior.&#160; Also I have heard of
different cichlid species interbreeding.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;The water was anywhere from a pH of 6.0 to
7.8-8.0. The ammonia and nitrates were around 0ppm, and again I never
tested the water. The only type of plants I keep were floating plants
like water lettuce as anything else was quickly uprooted. I have kept
very large pants with my Convicts and Firemouths but these were well
established and very large plants. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;Often it was beneficial to separate the
pair, with a tank divider, usually a piece of plexi glass prior to
breeding. The fish could see each other and water would go between the
two halves of the tank. A few days of this and then a water change at
the time of removing the divider would usually stimulate the pair to
lay eggs. I'd recommend reading about the species that you want to keep and
learning about its needs and size requirements. Convicts can be kept
with Firemouths and both grow to less than 6 inches. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;Usually I kept species tanks. The only
exception is in keeping Convicts with Firemouths. They are fairly
compatible if you get them when they are all small fish. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160; Convicts ([Cichlasoma/Herichthys]Archocentrus nigrofasciatus)&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Convicts are sexually dimorphic and usually easy to sex.
Females Convicts are more colorful. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are extremely aggressive towards other fish especially
when breeding and may kill other fish.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They could with stand just about any pH. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are egg layers where both parents raises the young,
although they may eat the eggs or young.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They may eat anything it can catch and fit in their mouth,
I fed them shrimp pellets, color bits, and other slow sinking
pellitized foods.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Male Convicts grow about 5 inches and females are about 4
inches.&#160; It also depends on the size of the tank that they are
kept in and what other fish are in there with them. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;I'd recommend at least a 10 gallon tank for
2 convicts.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Provide LOTS of hiding spaces. The more the better. &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160; Firemouths  ([Cichlasoma]Thorichthys meeki)&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Firemouths
are also sexually dimorphic, they are not that easy to sex. Male
Firemouths are usually red bellied while females
tend to have more white.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are semi-aggressive towards other fish especially
when breeding.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They could with stand just about any pH. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are egg layers where both parents raises the young,
although they may eat the eggs or young.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They may eat anything it can catch and fit in their mouth,
I fed them shrimp pellets.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Male Firemouths grow about 5 to 5-1/2 inches and females
are about 4 to 4-1/2 inches.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;I'd recommend at least a 15 gallon tank for 2 Firemouths.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Provide LOTS of hiding spaces. The more the better. &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
        </comment>
   </fish_data>
   <fish_data>
        <name>Bettas</name>
        <comment>
&#160;&#160; In my experience, bettas will live for about 2
years.&#160; I have read that they should live for 5 years, however
often this is not taking into account a few things.&#160; The first
thing to consider is that bettas when bought from a store are probably
already 6 months to 2 years old.&#160; The last pet shop I bought my
betta from, I decided to ask how old the fish was.&#160; They told me
that they were about 1-1/2 years old.&#160; Using that as my estimate
for how old the previous onces I got from that shop,&#160; I estimate
that one of my bettas died at about 3.5 to 4 years old.&#160; I'd
estimate that they lived on average for 1.5 years with me, and the oldest was 2 years old.&#160;
Not bad for a 5 dollar fish ( sometimes you can get them cheaper, but I get some pretty
nice ones, that I know they are healthy.)
&lt;p&gt;
&#160;&#160; Bettas grow to about 3 inches, give or take.&#160; There
are short fined and long finned varieties.&#160; I usually get the long
finned varieties.&#160; But I now own a shortfinned blue male.&#160; He
is very vibrant blue.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&#160;&#160; I feed them betta bits or other small floating pellitized
food.&#160; They seem to do fine with that.&#160; I am going to try to
feed them more live or frozen foods, but due to time constraints I find
it easier to feed them pellets.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&#160;&#160; While it is possible to keep a betta in a small container,
which they usually sell them in, I have found that it is better to get
a 3 gallon aquarium ( the Eclipse works great ) and get a tank divider
and a small heater.&#160; Using this method you can keep 2 bettas in
the tank and they will flare up their fins, and display to each other,
but wont kill each other.&#160; Also the heater keeps the tank at a
temperature above 72 degrees.&#160; While they can survive wihtout the
heater, I think that where I live it may get to cold.&#160; I have also
noticed that they do better with the heater and they seem to live
longer this way as well.&#160; The filter will also make it so that you
are not changing their water each week or twice a week.&#160; You can
acutally keep some small plants in the tank as well and gravel, and it
makes for a nice display tank.&#160;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&#160;&#160; To breed bettas a 5 gallon tank will work.&#160; Use lots
of floating plants like water lettuce or java moss, or something real
bunchy.&#160; Add a male and feed him well.&#160; Keep the water
temperature at about 75 to 80 degrees F.&#160; Then when the male
starts building a bubble nest add a ripe female.&#160; The female
should show dark verticle bands around her middle and she should have a
white tube showing on her abdomen.&#160; They pretty much do the rest.
&#160;&#160; Raising the babies is difficult and requires many
containers or a large tank.&#160; They seem to get territorial at an
early age.&#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&#160;&#160; Betta Splendens
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Sexually dimorphic, males usually have longer fins, females
will show dark verticle bands when in breeding condition.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Males are &lt;span style="font-weight: bold; font-style: italic;"&gt;extremely&lt;/span&gt;
aggressive towards their own kind, yet are often preyed upon in a
community tank, and will occasionally get
their fins nipped.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They can handle just about any pH within reason. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are egg layers and the eggs are really small, the male
will care for the egs, most of the time.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They may eat anything it can catch and fit in their mouth,
I fed them small pellets.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They grow about 3.5 to 4.5 inches, depending on various
conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;I'd recommend at least a 3 gallon with a divider for 2, or
a 2 gallon for a single fish, and a
5 gallon as a breeding tank for a pair.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
        </comment>
   </fish_data>

   <fish_data>
        <name>Livebearers</name>
        <comment>
      &#160;&#160;&#160;I have keep several of the more common live
bearer fish. This includes Swordtail's, Guppies, Platies, and Mollies.
My favorite is the guppy as I feel it is the most colorful of all these
fish with its blues, reds, blacks, greens, orchids, and more colors.
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;One thing to note is that pH and temperature
has always varied. I think that as long as the pH is somewhere between 6
and 8 most will do just fine and as long as the temperature is not
below 68 and not above 90 degrees they will do okay. Nitrates,
nitrites, and ammonia should be as close to zero as possible. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;Guppies are very easy to keep and breed, but
Platies, Swordtail's, and mollies are fairly easy as well. They are all
easy to sex and the fish do all the work. I just feed them ;-). Mollies
are a little more difficult than Guppies because Mollies require some
salt in the water and the conditions of the water to be a little
better. Swordtail's are a little aggressive and can be a little difficult to
keep in a community because of this. Lastly some Swordtail's and
Mollies can grow to be rather large compared to the Guppies and Platies. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;Sexing guppies is rather easy once they are
mature. The males have an extended anal fin (called the gonoponodium)
and in the fancy varieties the males are much more colorful than the
females. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;The method of breeding I first tried from
1993 to 1999 was selective line breeding. This is when you take a male
and mate it with a particular female usually its daughters and
granddaughters. In my case I was doing repetitive selective line
breeding. I mated males with their daughters and grand daughters. I
would select females based on size and the color of the female. For the
males I choose them based on their colors, size of the developing tail
and size of the fish. This worked out nice, but kept giving me very red
males and blue tailed females, even though I was trying for blue males.
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;While some people choose to breed one male
to two or three females, I was using one male to one female. This would
ensure that the female that got pregnant was the female that I wanted
and the male that I wanted as well. This went on for several years.
Occasionally I would out cross my fish to get some new genes in the
pool. This is a good method to create a new variety of guppy, however
the drawbacks are that it can weaken the fish, especially the immune
system. Many of the fancy male guppies I had ended up having trouble
carring their tails as they got older. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;As the fish grow they begin to show various
colors. The first color that I always is black on the tail. This of
course is in any species that I have kept that have had black in their
coloring. The next color is usually yellow and then red. I then see
colors like green appear and blue as well. So far it seems that red and
black are possibly the dominant color genes and blue is recessive. They
did show colors of green shine and blue shine when the light hit them
just right, but that was hard to see. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;I have also had some recent success with
Platies. I keep red and black Platies and I have had them breed as
well. They babies in this species resemble the parents identically, but
smaller. Unlike the guppies where the colors appear over time, the
Platies show color right away. Mollies are the same, especially the
black mollies. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;I've kept different types of livebearers
together in the same tank, but usually not for long periods of time.
Although I have never had them cross breed (breeding between species) I
have heard that it is possible. I'd recommend that in keeping
livebearers and mixing them, either keep them all of the same sex or
keep both sexes of all the species that you have in the tank. &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;Platies(Xiphophorus maculatus
	or variatus) / Guppies (Poecilia reticulata)&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Sexually dimorphic, males have gonopodium, which is an
extended anal fin.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are not aggressive and can be kept in a community,
occasionally they will nip fins of long finned fish or they may get
their fins nipped.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They could withstand just about any pH. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are live bearers, and may eat their young.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They may eat anything it can catch and fit in their mouth,
I fed them a shrimp treat flake food.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They grow about 1.5 to 4.5 inches, depending on various
conditions, and species.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;I'd recommend at least a 6 gallon for a pair or trio, and a
10 or 20 gallon as a breeding tank for about 6 to 12.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
        </comment>
   </fish_data>

   <fish_data>
        <name>Rosy Barbs</name>
        <comment>
&#160;&#160;&#160;I have keep Rosy Barbs for a few years.  They are pretty hardy fish that remind me of comet goldfish.  They are in the same family as goldfish.  They can live for a few years, and they are usually pretty active.  They are egg scatters, and they usually breed in the morning.  They come in albino or gold, rosy red-orange, and long finned varieties.  I was actually able to breed these fish pretty easily.  In fact they did it on their own before I
even tried anything.  All I did was harvest the eggs and then hatch them in a different container.
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Sexually dimorphic, males are usually rosy red and females are usually silver.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are not aggressive and can be kept in a community,
occasionally they will nip fins of long finned fish or they may get
their fins nipped.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They could withstand just about any pH. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are egg scatters and eat their young and eggs.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They may eat anything it can catch and fit in their mouth,
I fed them slow sinking pellet.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They grow about 4 inches, depending on various
conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;I'd recommend at least a 20 gallon for a group of 6.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
        </comment>
   </fish_data>

   <fish_data>
        <name>White Clouds</name>
        <comment>
&#160;&#160;&#160;I have kept White Cloud Mountain Minnows.  They are small fish, about 1.5 inches max.
These fish are easy to keep, however I find it best to keep then in a tank that has no gravel or anything on the bottom
of the tank.  Keeping the tank gravel free allows one to see how much food is not being eaten.  I have kept them in a small
container that is about a 4 to 5 gallon sized container.  Using just a sponge filter they can be kept fairly easily.  Water changes
can be done twice a week.  To breed them I use a small 3 gallon container with 3 spawning mops made out of green acrylic yarn.
One mop goes on the bottom the other two are suspended using styrofoam.  The tank has a small heater that can raise the temperature
3 or 4 degrees.  They seem to breed pretty quickly if the female is round and plump.  They will lay lots of eggs and can be removed
as soon as some eggs are spotted.  The eggs hatch in about 36 hours at about 75 degrees.  The fry will become darters about a
day after hatching. They should be feed 'green water' for the first few days.  After the first week, frozen baby brine shrimp can
be feed to the newly hatched fry. Water should be changed every 2 or 3 days in the fry tank depending on how big a tank
is used and how many fry are in there, however the environment should not be sterile.  The fry will eat microbes and bugs that
are in the tank.  Fry grow better if they have constant food and live food and clean water.  Greenish water or even water that
has green water dumped into it in small doses will have lots of little microbes for the fry to eat.  This works with most egg
scattering fish as well.
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Not really sexually dimorphic, females are slightly larger than males and when they are full of
effs females tend to be a lot fuller and males are slimmer. With both in a tank it is noticable.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They could withstand just about any pH. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are egg scatters and may eat their young and eggs.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They may eat anything it can catch and fit in their mouth,
I fed them slow sinking pellet ground up and sometimes freeze dried blood worms.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They grow about 1.5 inches, depending on various
conditions.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;I'd recommend at least a 5 gallon for a group of 6.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
        </comment>
   </fish_data>

   <fish_data>
        <name>Goldfish</name>
        <comment>
&#160;&#160;&#160;I have kept Goldfish for many years and have even breed them.  Goldfish are relatively large fish.
Goldfish tend to be messy fish and create a lot of waste so powerful filtration should be used.
Although some people have kept goldfish in small fish bowls, this is not a good practice as it will likely stunt their growth.
Many people think goldfish are not hardy because they keep them in subpar conditions and they fish die quickly. There should be 0 Ammonia in the tank.
If the fish do not last 5 years or more then you probably are doing something wrong.
      &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Not really sexually dimorphic, females are slightly larger than males and when they are in breeding condition the males might develop white pimples on their gills and pectoral fins.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;Most will adapt to just about any pH, but a pH of 7.0 would be good. &lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They are egg scatters and will eat their young and eggs.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They may eat anything it can catch and fit in their mouth,
I fed them Tetra Color sinking granules.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;They grow about over 5 inches, depending on various
conditions and what type, they could get to be 10 inches or more from head to tail.&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt;I'd recommend at least 30 gallons for the first fish, another 20 gallons for a second fish, and then after that 10-20 gallons for each additional fish.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;/ul&gt;
        </comment>
   </fish_data>

   <fish_data>
        <name>Bristol Nosed Cats</name>
        <comment>

        </comment>
   </fish_data>
</tropical_fish>
